[{"body": [{"type": "add-up-fill", "title": "填一填", "stem": "数一数，将花朵的数量填到相应的位置", "list": ["v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/0支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/1支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/2支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/3支花_2.svg"]}], "answers": [0, 1, 2, 3], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["0的认识"], "level": "1", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-8-02"}, {"body": [{"type": "add-up-fill", "title": "填一填", "stem": "数一数，将花朵的数量填到相应的位置", "list": ["v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/0支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/1支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/2支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/4支花-1.svg"]}], "answers": [0, 1, 2, 4], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["0的认识"], "level": "1", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-8-02"}, {"body": [{"type": "add-up-fill", "title": "填一填", "stem": "数一数，将花朵的数量填到相应的位置", "list": ["v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/0支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/1支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/2支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/5支花_2.svg"]}], "answers": [0, 1, 2, 5], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["0的认识"], "level": "1", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-8-02"}, {"body": [{"type": "add-up-fill", "title": "填一填", "stem": "数一数，将花朵的数量填到相应的位置", "list": ["v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/0支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/1支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/3支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/4支花-1.svg"]}], "answers": [0, 1, 3, 4], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["0的认识"], "level": "1", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-8-02"}, {"body": [{"type": "add-up-fill", "title": "填一填", "stem": "数一数，将花朵的数量填到相应的位置", "list": ["v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/0支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/1支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/3支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/5支花_2.svg"]}], "answers": [0, 1, 3, 5], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["0的认识"], "level": "1", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-8-02"}, {"body": [{"type": "add-up-fill", "title": "填一填", "stem": "数一数，将花朵的数量填到相应的位置", "list": ["v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/0支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/1支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/4支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/5支花-1.svg"]}], "answers": [0, 1, 4, 5], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["0的认识"], "level": "1", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-8-02"}, {"body": [{"type": "add-up-fill", "title": "填一填", "stem": "数一数，将花朵的数量填到相应的位置", "list": ["v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/0支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/2支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/3支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/4支花_2.svg"]}], "answers": [0, 2, 3, 4], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["0的认识"], "level": "1", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-8-02"}, {"body": [{"type": "add-up-fill", "title": "填一填", "stem": "数一数，将花朵的数量填到相应的位置", "list": ["v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/0支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/2支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/3支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/5支花_2.svg"]}], "answers": [0, 2, 3, 5], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["0的认识"], "level": "1", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-8-02"}, {"body": [{"type": "add-up-fill", "title": "填一填", "stem": "数一数，将花朵的数量填到相应的位置", "list": ["v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/0支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/2支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/4支花_2.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/5支花_2.svg"]}], "answers": [0, 2, 4, 5], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["0的认识"], "level": "1", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-8-02"}, {"body": [{"type": "add-up-fill", "title": "填一填", "stem": "数一数，将花朵的数量填到相应的位置", "list": ["v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/0支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/3支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/4支花-1.svg", "v2/通用/235数数/0-5支花/5支花-1.svg"]}], "answers": [0, 3, 4, 5], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["0的认识"], "level": "1", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-8-02"}]